Guide to the United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 Photographs, Part I: Negatives PHOTOS.023
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series I. Negatives, Bulk, 1940-1959; 1938-1969 (bulk 1940s-1950s)
  - Subseries I:B - Individuals - 1939-1969
    - Tonya, Rachel [Portrait Feature], Nov 2, 1948 (Negative 28568)
    - Toomer, Benjamin [Photographer Feature], Sep 17, 1947 (Negative 26604)
    - Top Officers of District 65 [Reverby, Andren, Michelson, Livingston, Robinson, Paley, Bernknopf] [Portrait Feature], Jul 2, 1956 (Negative 29081-29082)
    - Torres, Leo [Portrait Feature], Nov 20, 1953 (Negative 29020-29022)
    - Torres, Ralph [Photographer Feature], Dec 14, 1949 (Negative 27050)
    - Toubine, Julius [Photographer Feature], Nov 12, 1946 (Negative 26454)
    - Trade Union - Local Officers, Nov 17, 1952 (Negative 29582-29584)
    - Trainee Organizers, Feb 21, 1962 (Negative 19846)
    - Tregub, Phil [Portrait Feature], Sep 21, 1943 (Negative 28255)
    - Tronenfeld, Sandra - Sorting Christmas Greetings, Dec 15, 1944 (Negative 2038)
    - Truitt, John [Photographer Feature], May 14, 1948 (Negative 27479-27480)
    - Trumbull, Alec - Secretary Retail General, Feb 19, 1957 (Negative 15757-15760)
    - Tucker, Agnes [Photographer Feature], Apr 19, 1945 (Negative 26186)
    - Turban, Al [Portrait Feature], Aug 17, 1960 (Negative 29209)
    - Turkel, Irving [Portrait Feature], Oct 1, 1945 (Negative 28409)
    - Turkel, M. - U2 Temp. Organization, Apr 12, 1943 (Negative 1409)
    - Turner and Daughter [Portrait Feature], Dec 3, 1951 (Negative 28806)
    - Turner, Abe - Delivering Report [Capsule Biography Feature] [Portrait Feature]; [Portrait Feature] - Farm Supply Director (?), undated; Dec 18, 1944; Mar 6, 1944 (Negative 28222-28223; 28309; 28273)
    - Turner, Charles [Photographer Feature], Jul 14, 1953 (Negative 27157)
    - Turner, Helen [Photographer Feature], Mar 26, 1947 (Negative 26523; 26527)
    - Turnick, Annette [Photographer Feature], Jan 25, 1950 (Negative 27073)
    - Tutuiler, Harriet [Photographer Feature], Sep 20, 1944 (Negative 26087)
    - Twardzyk, Jack of Stern's - and Family (from Feature Art); [Balddinger], Dec 6, 1960 (Negative 18545-18556)
    - Tyler, Al [Capsule Biography Feature], Feb 1950 (Negative 28220-28221)
    - Ubogy, Wolf (?) [Portrait Feature], Apr 3, 1950 (Negative 28680)
    - Udintz, Julius [Portrait Feature], Nov 15, 1948 (Negative 28583)
    - Uhl, Mary; Security Plan Story, Apr 9, 1949 (Negative 5061-5063)
    - Ullman, Rose - Retired Gimbels Worker Sews Dresses for Needy Kids with the Aid of Retiree Hector Jacques, Oct 1964 (Negative 23407-23413)
    - Unger, Nat [Photographer Feature], Mar 30, 1949 (Negative 26901)
    - Unidentified - NAamm's (Department Store) Security Plan [Portrait Feature], Dec 22, 1949 (Negative 29796)
    - Unidentified [Photographer Feature] I, undated; Dec 11, 1945; Feb 6, 1946; Mar 20, 1946; Apr 2, 1946; May 29, 1946; Jun 12, 1946; Sep 16, 1946; Nov 12, 1946; Dec 17, 1946 (Negative 25691-25692; 26297; 26318; 26329; 26361; 26418; 26451-26456; 26490-26492)
    - Unidentified [Photographer Feature] II, Dec 17, 1946; Dec 24, 1946; Jan 22, 1947; Jan 24, 1947; Mar 3, 1947 (Negative 26498-26504; 26518; 26526; 26537; 26545; 26543)
    - Unidentified [Photographer Feature] III, Mar 26, 1947; Mar 29, 1947; Apr 29, 1947; May 26, 1947; Jun 24, 1947 (Negative 26551-26553; 26558-26559; 26569-26571; 26574-26580; 26663-26666)
    - Unidentified [Photographer Feature] IV, Jan 8, 1948; Feb 3, 1948; Feb 19, 1948; Apr 1, 1948; Jul 10, 1948 (Negative 26675-26676; 26681; 26692; 26716-26723; 26728-26736)
    - Unidentified [Photographer Feature] V, Jul 20, 1948; Aug 4, 1948; Oct 11, 1948; Nov 12, 1948; Jan 1949 (Negative 26749; 26758-26761; 26767-26770; 26811-26812; 26818-26821)
    - Unidentified [Photographer Feature] VI, Mar 2, 1949; Mar 9, 1949; May 26, 1947; Jul 8, 1947; Jul 22, 1947 (Negative 26828; 26849-26865; 26888-26889; 26897-26898; 27324-27358)
    - Unidentified [Portrait Feature] I, May 3, 1945; May 15; July 9; July 17; May 2, 1946; Sep 19, 1946; Nov 9, 1948; Nov 15, 1948; Nov 30, 1948; Jan, 1949; Sep 15, 1949; Oct 14, 1949 (Negative 28350; 28353; 28379; 28381; 28529; 28553-28554; 28577; 28582; 28586-28588; 28592; 28633; 28645-28646; 28648)
    - Unidentified [Portrait Feature] II, Dec 3, 1949; Dec 9, 1949; Dec 13, 1949; Dec 22, 1949; Jan 10, 1050; Apr 1, 1950; Aug 17, 1950; Aug 29, 1950; Sep 5, 1950 (Negative 28654; 28658; 28660; 28662; 28672; 28681-28682; 28717-28718; 28724; 28728)
    - Unidentified [Portrait Feature] III, Dec 21, 1950; Aug 20, 1951; Aug 30, 1951; Aug 30, 1951; Feb 14, 1952; Mar 17, 1952 (Negative 28746; 28770-28771; 28773; 28816-28817; 28830)
    - Unidentified [Portrait Feature] IV, Dec 5, 1952; Feb 3, 1953; Feb 14, 1953; Mar 3, 1953; Apr 8, 1953 (Negative 28898; 28918-28922; 28933-28935; 28948-28951; 28962)
    - Unidentified [Portrait Feature] V, Jun 15-16, 1953; Oct 6, 1953; Dec 21-22, 1953; Sep 25, 1956; Apr 21, 1957 (Negative 28990-28992; 28967-28978; 29026-29029; 29084-29088; 29094-29095)
    - Unidentified [Portrait Feature] VI, Mar 18, 1958; Undated; May 12, 1959; Aug 1959; Aug 8, 1960 (Negative 29107-29111; 29127-29135; 29145-29151; 29158-29165; 29191-29203)
    - Unidentified [Portrait Feature] VII, Undated; Undated; Nov 19, 1961; Apr 5, 1947; Mar 3, 1949 (Negative 29237-29239; 29249-29251; 29268; 29744; 29765-29768)
    - Unidentified Individuals, undated (Negative 25905-25907)
    - Unidentified Individuals - Club 65, Mar 25, 1953 (Negative 10517-10518)
    - Unidentified Individuals from Department Store Workers' Union [probably Local 1250], 1940's (Negative 30002-30008; 30010; 30015-30020; 30023-30025; 30029-30034; 30036)
    - Unidentified Local 65 Organizers [Portrait Feature], Sep 6, 1946 (Negative 29712-29723)
    - Unidentified Man [Portrait Feature], undated (Negative 29407-29408)
    - Unidentified Pension Plan Eligibles [Portrait Feature], Oct 14, 1949 (Negative 29788-29790)
    - Unidentified Portrait of a Man, Mar 3, 1941 (Negative 29762)
    - Unidentified Portrait of a Woman, Mar 3, 1941 (Negative 29761)
    - Unidentified Portraits - Pageant [Portrait Feature], Aug 13, 1951 (Negative 29816-29836)
    - Unidentified Speaker at Podium, undated (Negative 25697)
    - Unidentified Union Voice Committee Stewards [Portrait Feature], Sep 15, 1949 (Negative 29783-29787)
    - Unidentified Woman [Photographer Feature], Sep 18, 1945 (Negative 3246)
    - Unidentified Woman and Infant, 1952 (Negative 8392)
    - Union News Striker Gets Turkey, Nov 21, 1951 (Negative 8196)
    - Union Officials [Portrait Feature], undated (Negative 30080-30165)
    - Union Voice [Portrait Feature], Dec 13, 1945 (Negative 28445)
    - Unkel, William [Photographer Feature], Jun 28, 1954 (Negative 27277)
    - Upshur, Christine [Photographer Feature], Jan 1949 (Negative 26827)
    - Upshur, Lillian [Portrait Feature] [Capsule Biography Feature]; Dance to Celebrate Her Election As Co-Leader of Harlem District, undated; Feb 1951; May 15, 1956; Dec 18, 1959 (Negative 17791; 29077; 29413; 28224)
    - Urban, Stephen [Photographer Feature], Dec 10, 1953 (Negative 27224)
    - Uslaner, Morris [Photographer Feature], Oct 2, 1945 (Negative 26253)
    - Vacation Feature: 3rd Week of Vacations for Union Members Employed In Department Stores, Dec 31, 1953 (Negative 12258-12261)
    - Vails, William of Felsway Shoe - Retiring, May 13, 1955 (Negative 14071)
    - Valenta, Charles [Portrait Feature]; Former Bloomingdale's Stanford Worker [Portrait Feature], undated; Mar 1963; Apr 15, 1957 (Negative 25705; 29096-29097; 29342-29343)
    - Valenzuela, Rafael [Photographer Feature], Aug 8, 1944 (Negative 26069)
    - Valenzuela, Rafael, Jul 31, 1944 (Negative 1896)
    - Valle, Angel [Portrait Feature], May 14, 1962 (Negative 29271-29272)
    - Valle, Stanley [Photocopy], undated (Negative 25709)
    - Van Arsdale, Harry at 65 General Council (with David Livingston and Milton Reverby], Jun 3, 1959 (Negative 17352)
    - Van Brunt, John [Portrait Feature], Mar 21, 1956 (Negative 29069)
    - Van Delft, Peter of New Era Direct Mail - Hearn's Petition Getter, Sep 3, 1953 (Negative 11646)
    - Van Delft, Peter [Portrait Feature], Aug 1959 (Negative 29174)
    - Van Ness, Frances [Photographer Feature], Nov 26, 1946 (Negative 26461)
    - Van Sickles, Martin [Photographer Feature], Oct 1, 1946 (Negative 26422)
    - Varsity Team [Basketball], Dec 6, 1952 (Negative 10048-10054)
    - Veale, Mary - Lerner's, 1951 (Negative 7518-7520)
    - Vega Gonzalez, Juan of Vita Foods - Union Helped Get Him A New Home After Fire, Apr 6, 1964 (Negative 23169)
    - Velasquez, May 22, 1962 (Negative 20189)
    - Vendetta, Anthony [Photographer Feature], Jun 15, 1949 (Negative 26983-26984)
    - Venezia, Pat - Softball Star, Outfield [Portrait Feature], Jul 23, 1951 (Negative 28762)
    - Verdi, Joseph [Portrait Feature], Dec 13, 1945 (Negative 28443)
    - Vespa, Sal [Photographer Feature], Sep 4, 1949 (Negative 27005)
    - Vessiechio, Saverio S. [Photographer Feature], Sep 16, 1946 (Negative 26420)
    - Veteran Returns to District 65, Nov 29, 1945 (Negative 2420)
    - Veteran Returns to District 65, Nov 29, 1945 (Negative 2421-2425)
    - Vetter, Bill [Photographer Feature], Apr 1, 1948 (Negative 26735)
    - Veulf, Mary (Lerner), Sep 15, 1949 (Negative 5507)
    - Victor, Grace [Photographer Feature], Mar 26, 1947 (Negative 26524)
    - Vignali, Terry - Sak's, 34th St. - Christmas Feature [Portrait Feature], Nov 21, 1951 (Negative 28803)
    - Villiens, Grace [Photographer Feature], Feb 15, 1949 (Negative 26877)
    - Vim Committee Meeting [with Frank Brown], Oct 10, 1952 (Negative 9546)
    - Vim Employers [with Frank Brown?], Dec 1949 (Negative 5838)
    - Vim Steward, Jan 1950 (Negative 6071)
    - Virbisky [Portrait Feature], Aug 21, 1945 (Negative 28400)
    - Visch, Antonio [Photographer Feature], Jan 1, 1945 (Negative 26049)
    - Visiting Lincoln Memorial - Unidentified Individuals, Jun 1956 (Negative 22113-22115)
    - Vitamin Quota Committee, Dec 3, 1952 (Negative 10038-10042)
    - Vogel, Mildred [Photographer Feature], Sep 4, 1949 (Negative 27003)
    - Vogel, Stanley [Photographer Feature], Sep 4, 1946 (Negative 26409)
    - Volpe, Elviro [Photographer Feature], Oct 13, 1947 (Negative 26615-26616)
    - Wachtell, Phil (bottom) [Portrait Feature], Nov 9, 1948 (Negative 28575-28576)
    - Wachtell, Morris [Photographer Feature], Jun 26, 1946 (Negative 26366)
    - Wachtell, Phil - Going to the Army, Feb 1942 (Negative 975)
    - Wachtler, Saul [Photographer Feature], Jul 8, 1946 (Negative 26393)
    - Wacker, Leonard [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28225-28227)
    - Wagner, Robert, Mayor - Speaks At District 65 Executive Council Meeting, Oct 1, 1956 (Negative 15364-15366)
    - Wald, Jerry [Portrait Feature ], Sep 29, 1949 (Negative 28643)
    - Walker, Frances - Lerner Crew Party, May 29, 1945 (Negative 29523)
    - Walker, Nettie [Photographer Feature], Jan 25, 1945 (Negative 26144)
    - Walker, Peggy [Portrait Feature], Dec 3, 1961 (Negative 29257)
    - Wallace, Henry - at 13 Astor Place [District 65 Headquarters] [Unidentified Event, Wallace Speaking], 1948; Feb 9, 1948 (Negative 3523-3526; 4319-4324; 29610-29613)
    - Wallace, Joseph [Photographer Feature], Jul 1944 (Negative 26061)
    - Wallant, Chas [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28228-28230)
    - Walsh, Chris - Baseball Candidate for Giant Farm [Kerness- Photographer] [Portrait Feature], Feb 26, 1952 (Negative 28821)
    - Walters, Charles H. [Photographer Feature], Dec 10, 1947 (Negative 26645)
    - Walton, Lucille [Photographer Feature], Mar 6, 1946 (Negative 26310)
    - Wanderer, Margi ["Inquiring Photographer" Feature], Jul 6, 1949 (Negative 26985; 26987-26988)
    - Wantman, Mac [Capsule Biography Feature] [Portrait Feature], undated; Jan 17, 1944 (Negative 28231-28232; 28268-28268)
    - Ward, Bill [Photographer Feature], Jul 8, 1946 (Negative 26391)
    - Ward, Jim [Portrait Feature], Aug 18, 1960 (Negative 29208)
    - Warden, George - Pitcher, Softball All-stars [Portrait Feature], Jul 21, 1952 (Negative 28863)
    - Warfield, George [Photographer Feature], Feb 3, 1948 (Negative 26685)
    - Warman, Manny - New Voices Photographer - Joining Army [Portrait Feature], Apr 6, 1946; Sep 27, 1943 (Negative 1534; 28513)
    - Warner, Mildred [Photographer Feature] [Portrait Feature], Oct 15, 1946 (Negative 26433-26434; 28504)
    - Warshauer, Herb [Portrait Feature], Apr 4, 1946 (Negative 28510)
    - Warshauer, Herb - Saturday Night Social [Capsule Biography Feature], undated; Jun 1944 (Negative 1794-1795; 28234)
    - Warshauer, Michael [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28233)
    - Waxman, Betty [Photographer Feature], Apr 24, 1954 (Negative 27263)
    - Weatherby, Bridget [Portrait Feature], Aug 1959 (Negative 29172)
    - Weatherly, Goodhue Jr. [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28235)
    - Webber, John [Portrait Feature], Feb 17, 1953 (Negative 28940)
    - Weber, Sylvia [Photographer Feature], undated (Negative 26141)
    - Wechsler, Anna - Retiring, Jun 28, 1956 (Negative 15220-15222)
    - Wechsler, Milton [Photographer Feature], Apr 2, 1946 (Negative 26328)
    - Weener, Sunny [Capsule Biography Feature], Aug 12, 1952 (Negative 28236)
    - Wegene, Henry [Photographer Feature], Sep 20, 1944 (Negative 26090)
    - Weil, Gertrude - People of Distributive, Processing and Office Workers of America - Story [Portrait Feature], Dec 20, 1950; Jan 22, 1951 (Negative 28744; 28752)
    - Weinberg, Bernice [Photographer Feature], Jun 18, 1953 (Negative 27144)
    - Weiner, Mortimer [Photographer Feature], Mar 16, 1948 (Negative 26708-26709)
    - Weinstein, Dr. - Dental Lab, Jul 9, 1953 (Negative 11276)
    - Weinstein, Moe [P+B2852hotographer] [Portrait Feature], Apr 28, 1945 (Negative 28346)
    - Weinstein, Selig [Photographer Feature], Dec 14, 1949 (Negative 27049)
    - Weinstein, Sheila [Portrait Feature], Jun 25, 1962 (Negative 29297-29298)
    - Weinstock, Irving [Photographer Feature], Oct 15, 1946 (Negative 26435)
    - Weinstock, Louis and Arthur Osman - Construction -13 Astor Place, Jun 9, 1942 (Negative 1166)
    - Weintraub, Milton - Contest Winner [Portrait Feature], Feb 21, 1945 (Negative 28318)
    - Weisenfeld, Henrietta [Photographer Feature], Aug 19, 1947 (Negative 26589-26590)
    - Weiser, Irving [Portrait Feature], Feb 19, 1945 (Negative 28323)
    - Weiss - Osman Rally, Feb 28, 1940 (Negative 175-177)
    - Weiss, Mac, Sergeant [Portrait Feature], Apr 11, 1945 (Negative 28341)
    - Weiss, Mauriee, Second Vice President of Local 144 [Portrait Feature], Dec 7, 1946 (Negative 28563)
    - Weiss, Murray - Senior 65'ers, Jun 17, 1957 (Negative 15990-15991)
    - Weissman, Leon Lieutenant [Portrait Feature], Nov 23, 1945 (Negative 28433)
    - Weitzner, Newam [Portrait Feature], Jan 26, 1948 (Negative 29465)
    - Wells, Berroli [Photographer Feature], Feb 15, 1949 (Negative 26872)
    - Wells, Jeanette at Piano [Portrait Feature], Jan 9, 1946 (Negative 28459)
    - Wendell, Donald [Photographer Feature], Jul 29, 1953 (Negative 27167)
    - Wenzel, August Henry [Photographer Feature], Apr 2, 1946 (Negative 26325)
    - Werblun, Minnie [Photographer Feature], Aug 14, 1953 (Negative 27168)
    - Werner, Lou [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28237-28238)
    - West, Muriel - Arbitration Award for Corrugated Worker, Feb 1963 (Negative 21305-21310)
    - Wexler, Ann [Photographer Feature], Apr 1, 1948 (Negative 26729-26730)
    - Wharton [Portrait Feature], Apr 13, 1950 (Negative 28684; 28686)
    - Wharton, Virginia L. [Photographer Feature], Oct 26, 1949 (Negative 27020)
    - Whelan Worker, Jun 22, 1950 (Negative 6948; 29708-29809)
    - White Stokes, Amy [Portrait Feature], May 15, 1956 (Negative 29078)
    - White, George - Chicago, Local 194 [Capsule Biography Feature], Apr 1952 (Negative 28239)
    - White, Lillianon, May 15, 1942 (Negative 1099-1100)
    - White, Mary [Portrait Feature], Jul 28, 1950 (Negative 28705)
    - White, Richard [Portrait Feature], Feb 14, 1953 (Negative 28931)
    - Whitehorn, Bill, Private [Portrait Feature], Aug 3, 1943 (Negative 28253)
    - Whitehorn, Sam of Lerner's Shipping [Portrait Feature], Dec 17, 1956 (Negative 29091)
    - Whitfield, John [Photographer Feature], Dec 7, 1949 (Negative 27041-27042)
    - Whitfield, Linwood [Photographer Feature], Jun 15, 1949 (Negative 26967-26968)
    - Wicksler, Milton [Portrait Feature], Sep 6, 1945 (Negative 28404)
    - Wierner, Gert and Boss - Saying Good-bye, Sep 1942 (Negative 1249)
    - Wildfier, Mac - on Furlough [Portrait Feature], Aug 21, 1945 (Negative 28399)
    - Wilen, Scotty [Capsule Biography Feature], Aug 14, 1952 (Negative 28240)
    - Wilensky, Phil of A. S. Beck - Retiring, Jun 21, 1957 (Negative 15999-16000)
    - Williams, Eileen of Local 3 [Portrait Feature], Dec 23, 1947 (Negative 29460-29462)
    - Williams, Henry [Steward for C & C Butter], Oct 28, 1948 (Negative 4589)
    - Willis, Walter [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28241)
    - Willis, Walter [Photographer Feature], Dec 17, 1946 (Negative 26493-26493)
    - Willoughby, Lou of Columbia Textile Slitting - Delivered Baby in Emergency Near Shop [Portrait Feature], Jul 8, 1959 (Negative 29156-29156)
    - Willoughby, Roland - Modeling Consumer Service; New 'Bomber' Jackets [Portrait Feature], Jun 19, 1952; Jun 9, 1952; Feb 4, 1954 (Negative 12783-12784; 28836; 28839-28840)
    - Wilson, Herbert [Portrait Feature], Feb 17, 1953 (Negative 28941)
    - Wilson, Leslie - Local Officer [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 28242)
    - Wilson, Pauline (Fire Story), Jun 19, 1961 (Negative 19077-19078)
    - Wilson, Ralph - Trainee Organizer [Portrait Feature], Feb 26, 1953 (Negative 28946)
    - Wilson, Rebecca and Barbara - Mother and Daughter of Stern's Department Store - in Honor of Mothers Day; May 9, 1954, Apr 22, 1954 (Negative 12827-12829)
    - Winderman, Lillian [Photographer Feature], May 15, 1945 (Negative 26191)
    - Winkler, Rose [Photographer Feature], Sep 8, 1944 (Negative 26085)
    - Winocur, Harry [Portrait Feature], Oct 1, 1959 (Negative 29176)
    - Wishner, Julie, Lieutenant, May 23, 1944 (Negative 1778)
    - Wissoker, Theodore [Photographer Feature], Dec 17, 1946 (Negative 26484)
    - Withowski, Jul 11, 1947 (Negative 3084)
    - Wodin, Irv - Interviews Member, Nov 13, 1947 (Negative 29747)
    - Wolbrum, George [Photographer Feature], Jan 22, 1948 (Negative 26667)
    - Woldin, Irv [Capsule Biography Feature], Sep 19, 1947 (Negative 28243)
    - Wolehok Gives Prize to R. Vrech of 1-S, Dec 22, 1947 (Negative 3451)
    - Wolf, Mae [Photographer Feature], Sep 23, 1953 (Negative 27190)
    - Wolfe, Arque, Jan 14, 1946 (Negative 2467)
    - Wolff, Leo [Editor, New Voices] [Portrait Features], undated; Dec 27, 1944; Nov 7, 1951; Apr 11, 1961 (Negative 28311; 28793; 29242; 29488)
    - Wolfson, May [Photographer Feature], Aug 7, 1945 (Negative 26230)
    - Women's Auxiliary - Local 1199 [Portrait Feature], Feb 14, 1953 (Negative 28932)
    - Women's Basketball Team - Group Portrait, Jul 27, 1953 (Negative 11413)
    - Wood, Bonny (Feature on Poetry Book) [Portrait Feature], Jun 20, 1952 (Negative 28841)
    - Woodle, Ike of Stern's, Apr 9, 1951 (Negative 7716)
    - Worrell, Ralph - Election Candidate, May 21, 1962 (Negative 20166-20167)
    - Wortheimer, Larry, Jun 22, 1951 (Negative 29577-29578)
    - Wright and Feniello, Dec 8, 1951 (Negative 8213-8216)
    - Wright, Eve [Photographer Feature], Oct 15, 1946 (Negative 26436)
    - Wyatt, Walter - Trainee Organizer [Portrait Feature], Dec 15, 1960 (Negative 29240)
    - Wynn, Elmer (Slim) [Photographer Feature], Oct 29, 1947 (Negative 26626)
    - Yaffee, Sarah [Portrait Feature], Jul 28, 1950 (Negative 28707)
    - Yager, Evelyn [Photographer Feature], May 29, 1945 (Negative 26199)
    - Yazuin, Victor [Photographer Feature], Sep 2, 1954 (Negative 27299)
    - Yearwood, Randolph [Portrait Feature], Feb 7, 1946 (Negative 28484)
    - Yearwood, Sylvia [Photographer Feature], Jan 25, 1945 (Negative 26147)
    - Yolkofsky, Philip [Photographer Feature], Jul 25, 1945 (Negative 26222)
    - Yoshefiley, Rose - 195 Madison Street, NYC (with baby), Dec 1949 (Negative 5876-5878)
    - Young, Andrew [?], undated (Negative 25690)
    - Youngblood, Katherine [Photographer Feature], Aug 7, 1945 (Negative 26227)
    - Youngblood, Lester - Portrait, May 3, 1968 (Negative 25098-25099)
    - Zagl, Al - Retirement from Miles Shoe, Dec 22, 1956 (Negative 14549-14552)
    - Zaretsky, Ruth [Photographer Feature], undated (Negative 26349)
    - Zatorski, Karl and Lax Bargaeimer [Portrait Feature], Dec 1, 1961 (Negative 29258)
    - Zavattaro, Dean [Capsule Biography Feature] [Portrait Feature], undated, Sep 13, 1960; Sep 28, 1960 (Negative 28244; 29219; 29228)
    - Zeidel, Al [Portrait Feature], Feb 14, 1953 (Negative 28927)
    - Zelinske, Bruno, Private First Class [Portrait Feature]; [Photographer Feature], Sep 10, 1945; Dec 10, 1946 (Negative 26474; 28405)
    - Zelman, M. [Capsule Biography Feature], May 3, 1943; undated (Negative 1436-1437; 28245)
    - Zerfas, Frank [Portrait Feature], Jun 15, 1945 (Negative 28365)
    - Ziemar, Mabel [Photographer Feature], Apr 14, 1948 (Negative 27463-27464)
    - Ziering, Anna [Photographer Feature], May 26, 1947 (Negative 26546)
    - Ziff, Sol - Veteran [Portrait Feature], Oct 4, 1944 (Negative 28294-28295)
    - Zimmering, Carl [Photographer Feature] [Portrait Feature], Dec 3, 1946; Jun 11, 1945 (Negative 28360; 26469)
    - Zimmerman, Abe [Portrait Feature], Mar 10, 1947 (Negative 29422)
    - Zinn, Ann and Mike [Photographer Feature], Mar 31, 1954 (Negative 27256)
    - Zoldessy, William - Blood Donor [Portrait Feature] [Poster- CIO-PAC, Register ], Oct 9, 1944 (Negative 28297)
    - Zuckerberg, Harold [Photographer Feature], Jan 8, 1945; Jul 1944 (Negative 26284; 26060)
    - Zweigman, Loretta of Star Notion with Dog Rusty on the Job, Jul 29, 1953 (Negative 11421)
  - Subseries I:C - Locals Outside of New York City - 1943-1968
    - ALABAMA: Selma Local 112; Birmingham Locals at Annual Picnic; Montgomery, Apr 16, 1954; Aug 23, 1954; Mar 25, 1963 (Negative 12816; 13336 - 13345; 23862 - 23893)
    - ARKANSAS: Little Rock DPOWA (Distributive, Processing and Office Workers of America) [Security Plan Unification Steps]; Local 98; [racially integrated local], Apr 6, 1953; Jun 5, 1953; Aug 15, 1953 (Negative 10631 - 10632; 11065 - 11066; 11564)
    - CONNECTICUT: Bloomingdale Party for Stamford Workers, Dec 28, 1954 (Negative 13691 - 13692)
    - CONNECTICUT: Bloomingdale Strike in Stamford, Conn.; Sterns Members Picket Bloomingdale at Stamford; Bloomingdale Stamford Picketing, Feb 4, 1955; May 18, 1955; Sep 22, 1956 (Negative 13767 - 13787; 14117 - 14122; 15367 - 15380)
    - DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA: Shoe Chains' Strike, Washington D.C., Feb 1968 (Negative 25379 - 25406)
    - FLORIDA: Dade City, Local 43, DPOWA (Distributive, Processing and Office Workers of America): Leaders; Local 43 Meeting; Hobbs - Father and Son of Dade City; Local 43 New Building Site; Consumer Service and Negotiating Committee; Pasco Plant; Consumer Service and Christmas Tree; Elections; Political Action Committee With City Registr Clerk in Local Headquarters, 1951; Nov 1951; 1952; Feb 1952; Sep 7, 1952; Sep 22, 1952; Oct 5, 1952; Oct 19, 1952; Nov 2, 1952; Nov 30, 1952; Jan 3, 1953; Feb 2, 1953; May 7, 1954; Sep 1954 (Negative 8000 - 8003; 8183 - 8184; 9342 - 9354; 8494; 9414 - 9416; 9432 - 9436; 9490 - 9494; 9558 - 9559; 9841 - 9846; 10079 - 10085; 10160; 9774 - 9779; 12887 - 12889; 13402)